<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GameSpy</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to gamespy</string>
    <string name="goToLogo">Go to logo detection</string>
    <string name="setPicture">Set Picture</string>
    <string name="homeText">Welcome to GameSpy home menu</string>
    <string name="intoMain">Please tap the button below to go to the detection screen.</string>
    <string name="pictureInfo">Please press the button below and take a picture of the logo you want to look up! Please ensure your logo is taken at the center of your camera screen.</string>
    <string name="returnLogo">Return to Logo Detection</string>
    <string name="fortnite">Fortnite is a game developed by Epic games that is a battle royal style game currently free to play and a PvE game that is purchasable\n\n Tips:\n1: Burst assault rifles are very powerful at medium and close range, able to Ko a player with one burst.\n 2: You can get a friend to ride on a rocket you fire from a rocket launcher if you time the jump just right! </string>
    <string name="darkSoul">Dark souls is an action RPG made by From software and is widely claimed to be one of the toughest games out there on the market\n\n Tips:\n1: You can play Co-Op with friends by using a humanity and being a human from the bonfire, then accessing a friends summon sign from where they place it.\n 2:Monsters with torches look like weak enemies, but they'll always hit very hard so be careful.</string>
    <string name="skyRim">Skyrim is the fifth elder scrolls game developed by Bethesda studios. A game that has made its claim to fame through the development of Elder scrolls and Skyrim games.\n\n Tips:\n1: Save early and often\n 2: Interrupt enemies with Unrelenting Force.</string>
    <string name="superMario">Super mario is a long string of games of the Mario series made by nintendo, spanning across several consoles and widely revered as one of the great kings of videogames.\n\n Tips:\n1: Fire flower is usually best used when jumping.\n 2: Get to world 3/1, and become Super Mario. At the end of the level, by the staircase before the end flag, you will see two turtles coming down the stairs. Jumping over the first one and then jumping on the second one should cause it to hit the star and bounce back. From here, jump on it and keep yourself off the ground for unlimited 1ups. </string>
    <string name="clashOfClan">Clash of Clans is a freemium mobile strategy video game developed and published by Finnish game developer Supercell.\n\n Tips:\n1: Save Your Clash of Clans Gems in order to upgrade later.\n 2: Free Clash of Clans Gems. When you play you can earn free Clash of Clans gems by completing a variety of Clash of Clans Achievements or overcoming obstacles.  </string>

</resources>
